Blake Henriques Stephenson

647-678-3742 stephb7@mcmaster.ca blake-stephenson.github.io github.com/Blake-Stephenson linkedin.com/in/blake6

SKILLS

Electrical/Hardware:

- Soldering
- KiCad
- Circuit design
- Fusion
- Autodesk Inventor

Software:

- Python
- Raspberry Pi

October 2021

- Tkinter
- Flutter

- Beautiful soup
- CSS
- Java
- HTML
- C++
- JS
- MATLAB

EXTRACURRICULAR

MEC Sr. Design

Led team "Drip Systems" which placed first in the McMaster Engineering Competition, this qualified us to compete at the Ontario Engineering Competition. I worked on system integration for the sensors and motors with C++ to a microcontroller. I presented the project to a panel of judges and demonstrated how it functioned.

DeltaHacks 8 January 2022

Participated in DeltaHack8 where I worked on the UI using flutter for an app that allowed users to organize rallies and protests, Firebase was used to store user data.

Sumobots

February 2020

Design and built a robot for the Sumobots competition using C++ on an Ardunio.

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Electrical Engineering | GPA 3.7

McMaster University, Hamilton ON Sept 2019 - Apr 2023

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Testing Automation Engineer L3Harris

May 2022 - Present

Design, Develop and Support devices and their test applications (hardware and software). Test and maintain current test fixtures and assemblies

Glazier

FT Group

July 2021 - August 2021

Cut and installed windows, refined teamwork and communication by working in small groups while staying organized to maintain safety.

PROJECTS

Stock Tracker

A Raspberry Pi device that shows stock prices in real-time. Using python and a simple interface the user can select stocks that they would like to be updated on, the device then finds the prices using beautiful soup and prints them to an LCD display.

Lidar Mapping

Maps a user's room in 3D with Lidar.

Using a microcontroller coded with C a stepper motor, and a ToF sensor data is collected, the model of the room is made by creating a mesh with python.

Personal Website

Built a website to show off projects I've made, and improve HTML, CSS and JS skills.